http://holynativity.ca/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy:
Holy Nativity ("Holy Nativity")
operates http://holynativity.ca and may operate other websites. It
is Holy Nativity policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect
while operating our websites.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, Holy Nativity collects non-personally-identifying information of the
sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference,
referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Holy Nativity purpose in
collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand
how Holy Nativity visitors use its website. From time to
time, Holy Nativity may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by
publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
Holy Nativity also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol
(IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on http://holynativity.ca
blogs/sites. Holy Nativity only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same
circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that
commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site
where the comment was left.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to Holy Nativity websites choose to interact
with Holy Nativity in ways that require Holy Nativity to gather
personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Holy Nativity gathers
depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at http://holynativity.ca to provide a
username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Holy Nativity are asked to
provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to
process those transactions. In each case, Holy Nativity collects such information only insofar as
is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with
Holy Nativity. Holy Nativity does not disclose personally-identifying information
other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with
the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Aggregated Statistics
Holy Nativity may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its
websites. Holy Nativity may display this information publicly or provide it to others.
However, Holy Nativity does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as
described below.
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
Holy Nativity discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information
only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information
in order to process it on Holy Nativity behalf or to provide services available
at Holy Nativity websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some
of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by
using Holy Nativity websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to
them. Holy Nativity will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and
personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated
organizations, as described above, Holy Nativity discloses potentially personally-identifying and
personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or
when Holy Nativity believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the
property or rights of Holy Nativity, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered
user of an Holy Nativity website and have supplied your email address, Holy Nativity
may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to
date with what's going on with Holy Nativity and our products. If you send us a request (for
example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us
clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Holy Nativity takes all
measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of
potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser
provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Holy Nativity uses cookies to
help Holy Nativity identify and track visitors, their usage of Holy Nativity
website, and their website access preferences. Holy Nativity visitors who do not wish to have
cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before
using Holy Nativity websites, with the drawback that certain features
of Holy Nativity websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
Business Transfers
If Holy Nativity, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event
that Holy Nativity goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the
assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that
any acquirer of Holy Nativity may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this
policy.
Ads
Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies.
These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to
compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among
other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy
Policy covers the use of cookies by Holy Nativity and does not cover the use of cookies by any
advertisers.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Holy Nativity may change
its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Holy Nativity sole
discretion. Holy Nativity encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to
its Privacy Policy. If you have a http://holynativity.ca account, you might also
receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in
this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Search for:
Holy Nativity Anglican Church is located at: 12707 Bonaventure Drive S.E.
Calgary, Alberta, Canada.
T2J 4P4
You may reach the Holy Nativity Office at: 403 278 0001
holynat@home.com
Our office hours are:
Terrific Inspiration – Scott Garcia
Twitter Timeline:
#church Tweets
Archives:
December 2020 (10)
November 2020 (24)
October 2020 (54)
September 2020 (55)
August 2020 (214)
July 2020 (300)
June 2020 (43)
May 2020 (36)
April 2020 (13)
March 2020 (31)
February 2020 (91)
January 2020 (55)
December 2019 (112)
November 2019 (42)
October 2019 (136)
September 2019 (153)
August 2019 (75)
July 2019 (105)
June 2019 (95)
May 2019 (128)
April 2019 (151)
March 2019 (11)
February 2019 (34)
January 2019 (30)
December 2018 (30)
November 2018 (59)
October 2018 (86)
September 2018 (57)
August 2018 (72)
July 2018 (79)
June 2018 (134)
May 2018 (215)
April 2018 (259)
March 2018 (226)
February 2018 (160)
January 2018 (153)
December 2017 (131)
November 2017 (27)
October 2017 (33)
September 2017 (2)
July 2017 (4)
June 2017 (32)
May 2017 (2)
Recent PostsIndiaand now indonesia!Truly great peopleAs a busy mom of 10My Cornish MinerSleeping on an AirplaneThey see me alone and their eyes grow big...Waking up in IstanbulI have realized that this journey isnt a hobby or toy...Over the the 2 decades of youth work, both as paid and volunteer, I have...I often teach my clients that its not okay to manipulate...Thoughts on Marriage!!!This post is dedicated to my coach...Im not a numerologist...Ive long considered myself a ghandi fan-boy.Two investigators came to church...Placing children in the RIGHT homesFilled with the Spirit, Loving God An Incredible Solution and the Story Behind the StoryA woman of child-bearing age who couldnt get pregnant in biblical...About the original 12 Disciples...Feast of Tabernacles 2007
